laserfiche.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Laserfiche

NOTICE: This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 1, 2018.

Welcome to the Laserfiche.com website (the “Site”). This Site is operated by Compulink Management Center, Inc. doing business as Laserfiche and its affiliates (“Laserfiche”, “we”, “us”, “our”). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how information is collected and used by Laserfiche. We refer to all products and services offered by Laserfiche and the Site, including its content and functionality, as the “Services.” We are committed to taking appropriate steps to help protect the privacy of visitors to our Site or users of our Services.

 **By accessing or using the Site or our Services, you agree to be bound by this Policy and are accepting and consenting to the collection, use, disclosure, and other handling of your information as described below.** If you are entering into the terms of this Policy on behalf of a company, organization or another legal entity (an “ **Entity** “), you are agreeing to this Policy for that Entity and representing to Laserfiche that you have the authority to bind such Entity and its affiliates to this Policy, in which case the terms “ **you”** or related terms herein shall refer to such Entity and its affiliates. If you do not have such authority, or if you do not agree with this Policy, you must not accept these terms and may not use the Site or Service.

EU data protection law makes a distinction between organizations that process personal data for their own purposes (known as “controllers”) and organizations that process personal data on behalf of other organizations (known as “processors”). Laserfiche may act as either a controller or a processor in respect of your personal data, depending on the circumstances.

Laserfiche, located at the address in the section entitled “Contact Us” below, is the controller with respect to information you provide through the Site.

Sometimes Laserfiche operates as a processor on behalf of a customer, a separate legal entity, which is the data controller. For example, Laserfiche provides cloud services to its customers and processes personal data on their behalf to provide those services. Please visit the applicable customer’s privacy policy for information about their privacy practices. Any questions that you may have relating to such personal data and your rights under data protection law should therefore be directed to the customer as the controller, not to Laserfiche.

## 1\. Information We Collect

When you visit or use the Site and/or Services, we collect and retain information that you, as a customer or potential customer, provide through the Site or Services, as well as information that is automatically or passively collected from you, your device or your browser.

### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information that you provide directly to us. For example, when you manage your user profile, participate in interactive features (such as the Contact page), request newsletters or other marketing communications, request customer support, provide other information in connection with a job opening, enter login information, or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect includes:

  * Contact and profile information, including your name, email address, company information, postal address (including zip code), and telephone number;
  * Account and log-in information, including your username, password, login details, transaction details;
  * Credit card information and transaction details (if applicable);
  * Communications to us, for example, reporting a problem or submitting queries, concerns or comments regarding the Site or its content;
  * Resume and related data as necessary to consider you for a job opening if you submit an application to us, including your employment history, transcript, writing samples, and references; and
  * Any other content or information you choose to provide, including photos you may upload.

If you post information on the Site, including on a bulletin board, or in a chat room or community forum, it becomes generally available to the public. Laserfiche does not control or limit the use by visitors of the Site. By posting information on the Site, you are agreeing that Laserfiche may use the information in connection with its business. Therefore, you should not post any information you consider private or sensitive.

### Information We May Collect Automatically

We automatically collect information about your device and how your device interacts with our Site and the Services. We may use Service Providers to collect this information. Some examples of information we collect include the following:

  * Information about your visits to the Site and use of the Services, the resources you access, any data you download, and information related to the ways in which you interact with the Site or the Services;
  * IP addresses, including the general information in such address, such as city, state and zip code, unique device identifiers, other information about your mobile phone or other mobile device(s), browser types, and browser language;
  * Referral pages and links, URLs, number of clicks, pages viewed, how long you’re on a page, your search queries and results;
  * Information about your device, computer and/or browser you use, as well as the device’s operating system, such as device hardware model, operating system version, or mobile network information; and
  * Data about your device’s location, which can be precise (e.g., latitude/longitude data) or imprecise (e.g., location derived from an IP address or data that indicates a city or postal code level).
  * We use various current – and later – developed technologies to collect this information (“Tracking Technologies”), as further discussed below.

### Information We Collect From Customers

We provide products and services for our customers, and collect and process information about individuals (including through Tracking Technologies) at the direction of our customers (“Customer Data”). Customer Data has historically included contact data, demographic data, content, service use data, device connectivity and configuration data, and location data, among other information. Our processing of Customer Data is governed by the terms of our Cloud Service Agreements with our customers. To the extent we combine Customer Data with information we have collected about you through the Site, we will treat the combined information in accordance with the practices described in this Privacy Policy, plus any additional restrictions imposed by our customers. We are not responsible for how our customers treat the information we collect on their behalf, and we recommend you review their own privacy policies.

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may obtain information from other third party sources that we combine with information collected through the Site. These third party sources vary over time, but have included:

  * Data brokers from which we purchase demographic data to supplement the data we collect.
  * Social networks when you reference our Service or grant permission to Company to access your data on one or more of these services.
  * Partners with which we offer co-branded services, sell or distribute our products, or engage in joint marketing activities.
  * Publicly-available sources such as open government databases or other data in the public domain.

For example, if you log into a social media website through our Site, we may have access to certain information from that website, in accordance with the procedures and practices of that social media site.

You should carefully review the privacy policies and terms of use of these third parties.

## 2\. How Laserfiche Uses and Shares the Information We Collect

Laserfiche collects and uses the information you provide in connection with our Site and Services for our legitimate interests, including to:

  * Manage our Site and Services, including your registration and account;
  * Perform services requested by you, such as to respond to your comments, questions, and requests, and provide customer service;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, information regarding changes to our policies, and support and administrative messages;
  * Prevent and address fraud, breach of policies or terms, and threats or harm;
  * Keep you informed regarding Laserfiche and our software and services;
  * Develop and send you direct marketing, including advertisements and communications about our and third party products, updates, special offers, promotions, rewards, events, and services;
  * Help Laserfiche enhance products and services;
  * Contact you for market research and to survey your satisfaction with Laserfiche software and services;
  * Encourage you to participate in our user groups and invite you to events that may be of interest, including trainings, webinars, and conferences;
  * Improve our Site; and
  * Analyze information for trends and statistics, which may entail providing this information to an agent acting on Laserfiche’s behalf to assist in data analytics.

If you supply Laserfiche with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you supply us with your telephone number online, you may receive telephone calls from us with information regarding orders and/or requests you have placed online – such as a software demonstration request or general business inquiry.

If you supply Laserfiche with your email address, you may receive email messages from us for marketing purposes such as providing information on new products and services or upcoming events. We may track when you open our e-mail messages or click on the links contained within them.

We also use information about you with your consent, including to:

  * Serve advertising tailored to your interests on our Service and Third Party Services; and
  * Fulfill any other purpose disclosed to you and with your consent.

Some of our lawful bases for processing your information stem from our customers on whose behalf we provide services.

We may use information that does not identify you (including information that has been de-identified) without obligation to you except as prohibited by applicable law.

The information we collect may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Laserfiche maintains business operations. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and as permitted under applicable law.

### Sharing with Service Providers

We will occasionally hire other companies or contract with third-party consultants to provide limited services on our behalf. Laserfiche will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver services, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

We may share your information with approved third parties for marketing purposes; this may include our authorized resellers, user group training partners, and cloud solution providers. We may also share your information with third parties who provide services to assist us with our business activities.

Some information about your use of the Site and Services and certain Third Party Services may be collected using Tracking Technologies across time and services and used by us and third parties for purposes such as to associate different devices you use, and deliver relevant ads and/or other content to you on the Site, Services, and certain Third Party Services.

### Sharing with Others

We also share information about you as follows:

  * Affiliates. We may share your information with our related entities including our parent and sister companies. For example, we may share your information with our affiliates for customer support, marketing, and technical operations.
  * Customers. We share your information with our customers in connection with us processing your information on their behalf. For example, we share your information with our customers in order to facilitate your orders, maintain and administer your online accounts, respond to your questions and comments, comply with your requests, market and advertise to you, and otherwise comply with applicable law.
  * Business Partners. We may share your information with our business partners in connection with offering you co-branded services, selling or distributing our products, or engaging in joint marketing activities. For example, we may share information about you with a retailer for purposes of providing you with product support.
  * Promotions. Our promotions may be jointly sponsored or offered by third parties. If you voluntarily choose to enter a promotion, we may share your information with third parties a set forth in the official rules that govern the promotion as well as for administrative purposes and as required by law (e.g., on a winners list). By entering a promotion, you agree to the official rules that govern that promotion, and may, except where prohibited by applicable law, allow the sponsor and/or other parties to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing materials.
  * User Group, Training, and Events. Our events may be jointly sponsored or offered by third parties. If you voluntarily sign-up for an event through Laserfiche, we may share your contact details or information that you provide with the sponsor, facility, or any other organization who we schedule you to meet with at that event in order to fulfill your event registration and/or inform you of future events organized by the sponsor, which we believe you may be interested in.
  * Third Parties. We may share your information with third parties for purposes of facilitating your requests (such as when you choose to share information with a social network about your activities on the Site or Services) and in connection with tailoring advertisements, measuring and improving our Service and advertising effectiveness, and enabling other enhancements.
  * Consent. We may share your information for any other purpose disclosed to you and with your consent.

We reserve the right to share your information to respond to duly authorized requests from governmental authorities as required by law, or in circumstances in which we believe disclosure is necessary or reasonably appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or others. Please note that Laserfiche is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Some of the hyperlinks on our Site may lead to third-party websites that are not controlled by or affiliated with Laserfiche (“Third Party Services”). These links are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by Laserfiche of the content on such third-party websites. If you use our Services, which include third-party integration(s), such Services are also subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of each applicable third-party entity. For example, Office Online is a Microsoft service and use of Office Online is subject to Microsoft’s terms of use and privacy policy. Laserfiche is not responsible for and does not endorse, guarantee or monitor the content, availability, viewpoints, products or services that are offered or expressed on such third-party websites and does not make any representations or warranties regarding the content or accuracy of any content on these third-party websites, including third-party privacy policies.

Without limiting the foregoing, in our sole discretion, we may share aggregated information which does not identify you or de-identified information about you with third parties or affiliates for any purpose except as prohibited by applicable law.

Except as described in this Policy and our Cloud Services Agreement, we will not sell, rent, or in any way intentionally disclose personal information that you provide to us on the Site to any third party (other than a Service Provider or agent acting on our behalf as described above), unless: (a) we are required to do so by law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or court order, (b) we are required in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Laserfiche employees, users of Laserfiche products or services, or members of the public, or to enforce the Terms of Use; or (c) such disclosure is part of a sale of all (or substantially all) of the assets of one or more divisions or affiliates of Laserfiche.

## 3\. How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals

Do-Not-Track (DNT) is a preference that can be set in your browser to notify websites you visit that you do not want them to collect certain information about you. Laserfiche does not respond to DNT signals at this time. As discussed in this Policy, we and third parties may track your visits to our Site to provide targeted advertising.

## 4\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies And Choices Regarding the Same

We use Tracking Technologies to collect information, including the following:

  * Cookies. We may send cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that act as a unique tag to identify your browser. These cookies help us to improve our Services and your experience. These cookies allow our Site to recognize your device to save preferences and settings for you, such as your session information. We use two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate the Service and expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies help with personalizing your experience, remembering your preferences, and supporting security features. Additionally, persistent cookies allow us to bring you advertising both on and off the Service. Persistent cookies may remain on your device for extended periods of time, and generally may be controlled through your browser settings. Most browsers accept cookies by default. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to decline or delete cookies. If you use multiple browsers on your device, you will need to instruct each browser separately. Your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.
  * Log Files. A log file is a file that records events that occur in connection with your use of the Service, such as your service use data.
  * Pixels. A pixel (also known as a web beacon) is code embedded in a website, video, e-mail, or advertisements that sends information about your use to a server. There are various types of pixels, including image pixels (which are small graphic images) and JavaScript pixels (which contains JavaScript code). When you access a website, video, e-mail, or advertisement that contains a pixel, the pixel may permit us or a third party to drop or read cookies on your browser. Pixels are used in combination with cookies to track activity by a particular browser on a particular device. We may incorporate pixels from third parties that allow us track our conversions, bring you advertising both on and off the Service, and provide you with additional functionality, such as the ability to connect our Service with your social media account.
  * Device Fingerprinting. Device fingerprinting is the process of analyzing and combining sets of information elements from your device’s browser, such as JavaScript objects and installed fonts, in order to create a “fingerprint” of your device and uniquely identify your device and apps.
  * App Technologies. There are a variety of tracking technologies that may be included in our apps, and these are not browser-based like cookies and cannot be controlled by browser settings. For example, our apps may include third party SDKs, which is code that sends information about your use to a server, and is in effect the app version of a pixel. These SDKs allow us track our conversions, bring you advertising both on and off the Service, and provide you with additional functionality, such as the ability to connect our Service with your social media account.
  * Location-Identifying Technologies. GPS, WiFi, Bluetooth, and other location-aware technologies may be used to collect precise location data when you enable location-based services through your device. Location data may be used for purposes such as verifying your device’s location and delivering or restricting relevant content and advertising based on that location.

We use tools such as “Google Analytics” and others to track the usage of this Site. Google Analytics collects information, which may include, but is not limited to, what pages are visited on the Site or what browser is used to view the Site. We use the information provided by Google Analytics to improve our Site and services. You may view how Google uses data when you use our Site by visiting Google’s Terms of Service located at: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you by disabling cookies on your browser. You can opt-out of your data being used by Google Analytics through cookies by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and downloading the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

We also work with ad serving services, advertisers, and other third parties to serve advertisements on the Site, Services, and/or on Third Party Services. These third parties may use Tracking Technologies on our Sites, Services, and Third Party Services (including in e-mails and advertisements) to track your activities across time and services for purposes of associating the different devices you use, and delivering relevant ads and/or other content to you on the Site, Services, and Third Party Services or third party devices after you have left the Service (“Interest-based Advertising”).

We serve ads on and through Third Party Services, such as Facebook. LinkedIn and Google, that are targeted to reach people (or people similar to people) who have visited our Site or are identified in one or more of our databases (“Matched Ads”). This is done by us uploading a customer list to the Third Party Service or incorporating a pixel from the Third Party Service on our Site, and the Third Party Service matching common factors between our data and their data. To opt-out of receiving Matched Ads, please contact the applicable Third Party Service. If we use Facebook Custom Audiences to serve Matched Ads on Facebook services, you should be able to hover over the box in the right corner of such Facebook ads and find out how to opt-out. We are not responsible for such Third Party Service’s failure to comply with your opt-out instructions.

You can reset your device advertising Id at any time through your device settings, which is designed to allow you to limit the use of information collected about you. For information on how to do this on Apple devices, visit Apple.com. For information on how to do this on Android devices, visit Google.com. You can stop all collection of information via an app by uninstalling the app.

The location data collected through an app depends on your device settings and app permissions. You can exercise choice over the location data collected through our apps by (i) for GPS data, disabling location in your device settings or disabling location permissions to that app; (ii) for Bluetooth data, disabling Bluetooth and any Bluetooth scanning option in your device settings; or (iii) for WiFi data, disabling WiFi and any WiFi scanning option in your device settings. You can stop collection of all location data via an app by uninstalling the app.

Some of the third parties that collect information from or about you on the Site or Services in order to provide more relevant advertising to you participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. This program offers a centralized location where users can make choices about the use of their information for online behavioral advertising. To learn more about the DAA and your opt-out options for their members, please visit (i) for website opt-out, https://www.aboutads.info/choices; and (ii) for mobile app opt-out, https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices. In addition, some of these third parties may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, please visit https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. Please note that if you opt-out of online behavioral advertising using any of these methods, the opt-out will only apply to the specific browser or device from which you opt-out. Further, opting-out only means that the selected members should no longer deliver certain Interest-based Advertising to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads (e.g., from other ad networks). We are not responsible for effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their programs.

You may also limit our use of information collected from or about your mobile device for purposes of serving online behavioral advertising to you by going to your device settings and selecting “Limit Ad Tracking” (for iOS devices) or “Opt out of Interest-Based Ads” (for Android devices).

Please be aware that if you disable or remove Tracking Technologies some parts of the Service may not function correctly.

## 5\. Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms

Occasionally, portions of the Site may allow you to post information that other visitors to the Site will be able to access (i.e., a “bulletin board” or interactive “chat”).  If you choose to post information on a bulletin board or through a chat session, it becomes available to the public, and Laserfiche has no ability to control or limit its use.  Laserfiche and its affiliates have a right to utilize any information you post through the Site in connection with the operation of its business. Laserfiche encourages you not to post any information you consider private or sensitive on the Site.

## 6\. Your Privacy Rights: Controlling Your Personal Information (Access and Removal)

You have the right to access your personal data. Please contact our Data Protection Officer using the information set forth in the “Contact Us” section below to exercise such right. Visitors of this Site may request to have their personal information removed from our database, limit the use and disclosure of such information, or withdraw previously given consent to use such information for any of the purposes stated above. We may require additional information from you to allow us to confirm your identity. We will respond to all requests for review or removal of personal information within a reasonable time. Please note that we will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. California residents and data subjects in Europe may have additional rights as set forth in the sections entitled “California Privacy Rights” and “European Privacy Rights” below. For more information about choices regarding tracking technologies, see the section on “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies and Choices Regarding the Same” above.

You can opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails from us at any time by following the instructions as provided in e-mails to click on the unsubscribe link, or e-mailing us at the e-mail address set forth in the section entitled “Contact Us” below with the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject field of the e-mail. Please note that you cannot opt-out of non-promotional e-mails, such as those about your account, transactions, servicing, or Laserfiche’s ongoing business relations.

If you have opted-in to receive push notification on your device, you can opt-out at any time by adjusting the permissions in your device or uninstalling our app.

Please note that your opt-out is limited to the e-mail address, device, and phone number used and will not affect subsequent subscriptions.

## 7\. California Privacy Rights – California Customers

Customers in the state of California may request a list of categorized third parties and in some cases affiliates to whom we may have disclosed their personal information specifically for those third parties’ and/or affiliates’ own marketing purposes, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit a written request to the email or address provided below. Requests must include “California Privacy Rights Request” in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. Please note that we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the provided e-mail address or mail address.

## 8\. European Privacy Rights – Individuals in the European Union

If you are a data subject in Europe, you may have the right to access, rectify, or erase personal data we have collected about you through the Site or Services. You may also have the right to data portability and the right to restrict or object to our processing of personal data we have collected about you through the Site or Services. In addition, you have the right to ask us not to process your personal data (or provide it to third parties to process) for marketing purposes or purposes materially different than for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. You may withdraw your consent at any time for any data processing we do based on consent you have provided to us.

To exercise any of these rights, contact us as set forth in the section entitled “Contact Us” below and specify which right you intend to exercise. We will respond to your request within 30 days. We may require additional information from you to allow us to confirm your identity. Please note that we store information as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected, and may continue to retain and use the information even after a data subject request for purposes of our legitimate interests, including as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent fraud, and enforce our agreements.

We acknowledge that you have rights in connection with Customer Data. If your information has been processed by us on behalf of a customer and you wish to exercise any rights you have with such information, please inquire with our customer directly. If you wish to make your request directly to us, please provide the name of the customer on whose behalf we processed your information. We will refer your request to that customer, and will support them to the extent required by applicable law in responding to your request.

If you have any issues with our compliance, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a European supervisory authority.

## 9\. E.U./U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Compliance

Laserfiche complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Laserfiche has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles (“ **Principles** ”). If there is any conflict between the terms in this Notice and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

Laserfiche has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to the American Arbitration Association, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please contact or visit the American Arbitration Association for more information or to file a complaint. When filing by mail or email, please complete the appropriate Privacy Shield Program Notice of Arbitration Form located in the link below and forward to the International Centre for Dispute Resolution.

International Centre for Dispute Resolution Case Filing Services

1101 Laurel Oak Road, Suite 100  
Voorhees, NJ 08043  
United States  
Phone: +1.212.484.4181  
Email box: casefiling@adr.org

For any questions or for further information about this program, the ICDR’s International Arbitration Rules, or with additional language versions of the ICDR’s International Arbitration Rules, please contact the International Centre for Dispute Resolution at +1.212.484.4181 or by visiting the website <https://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html>. The services of the American Arbitration Association are provided at no cost to you.

Laserfiche is subject to the jurisdiction of the Federal Trade Commission, or any other applicable U.S. authorized statutory body, for purposes of Privacy Shield enforcement. Laserfiche is liable under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles for its agents to process transferred personal information in a manner consistent with the Principles. In addition, Laserfiche commits to cooperate with the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

Under certain limited circumstances, data subjects, as defined by the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016, of the European Union, may invoke binding Privacy Shield arbitration as a last resort if all other forms of dispute resolution have been unsuccessful. To learn more about this method of resolution and its availability to you, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

## 10\. Security Measures

We have implemented industry standard controls, intrusion detection network monitoring, and reasonable security measures designed to protect the personal information that you submit through the Services and Site.  These measures include physical access controls, access authorization controls, and firewalls. We also periodically review our information collection, storage, and processing practices to help prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alteration or other destruction of information we collect. When accessing secure sections of the Site, we use Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption to secure the communication of information passing between your browser and our servers. Additionally, only authorized administrators, Laserfiche employees and third-party contractors have access to systems containing such information. Please note that Laserfiche is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Nevertheless, transmission via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your information.

## 11\. Privacy of Children

The Site and Services are intended for a general audience and not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age. We do not market products or services to children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information as defined by the U.S. Children’s Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) in a manner that is not permitted by COPPA. If you are a parent or guardian and believe Company has collected such information in a manner not permitted by COPPA, please contact us as set forth in the section entitled “Contact Us” below, and we will remove such data to the extent required by COPPA.

## 12\. Translation

The English language version of this Policy and any notice or other document relating to this Policy shall prevail if there is a conflict except where the document is a constitutional, statutory or other official document.

## 13\. Privacy Policy Changes

Laserfiche reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event of a material change, this Privacy Policy will indicate the substance of the material change and its effective date at the very beginning of the Privacy Policy. Laserfiche recommends that you review this Privacy Policy regularly for any revisions. Your continued use of the Site or Services after such revisions will constitute your: (a) acknowledgement of the amended Policy and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the amended Policy.

## 14\. Contact Us

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please send a message to:

Compulink Management Center, Inc. d/b/a Laserfiche  
ATTN: Legal Department  
3545 Long Beach Blvd.  
Long Beach, CA 90807  
USA  

For EU-specific requests, you can reach our Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) at [privacy@laserfiche.com](mailto:privacy@laserfiche.com).
